Guide to the Association for Union Democracy: Women's Project Records WAG 331
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Association for Union Democracy: Women's Project Records
1947-2004 (Bulk 1980-2002)
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Association for Union Democracy
Association for Union Demoracy. Women's Project
Biers, Carl
LaTour, Jane
WAG 331
20 Linear Feet (20 boxes)
The Association for Union Democracy: Women's Project Records describe the activities and work of the Women's Project from its creation in 1985 into the early 2000s. These files include printed ephemera, newsletters and circulars, correspondence, serial publications, court cases, and organizational reports. The collection contains both records created and collected by the Women's Project that correspond to its work and mission as an advocate for women in unions and nontraditional trades, as part of the larger organization Association for Union Democracy. NOTE: This collection is stored offsite, and advance notice is required for use.
Conditions Governing Access
Mateirals are open without restrictions.
Arrangement
Files are arranged alphabetically. The collection is organized into three series.
Missing Title
Series I. Association for Union Democracy, 1979-2002
Series II. The Women's Project, 1971-2002
Series III. Subject and Organization Files, 1974-2004
Historical/Biographical Note
The Women's Project is a national advocacy project, created and funded by the Association for Union Democracy (AUD). The AUD was founded in 1969 as a permanent organization to help protect the democratic rights of unionists and considers itself a national, pro-labor, non-profit organization dedicated to advancing the principles and practices of democratic trade unionism in the North American labor movement. The organization created a national network of unionists, civil libertarians, labor educators, workers rights attorneys, law professors, and others who share the same goal. In 1985 AUD created the Women's Project, directed by Susan Jennik, to offer guidance and assistance to women unionists on utilizing their rights in unions and under the law to enable them to campaign effectively for equal rights in their unions and on the job.
The AUD Women's Project developed a network of women's groups from around the country and held its first conference titled "Women in Unions," in November of 1986. In the years since, the Women's Project has held numerous conferences, workshops, and seminars on issues of harassment, union rights, and women in nontraditional trades. AUD's monthly publication, Union Democracy Review, provides a forum for women unionists to publicize their work and recommend resources and exchange information about issues experienced by women in unions and in the workplace. In the early 1990s, the Women's Project published Manual for Survival for Women in Nontraditional Trades, which was then revised in 2000. Also in 2000 the Women's Project, then under the direction of Jane LaTour, launched "Operation Punchlist," to focus public attention on the barriers still facing women in nontraditional jobs.
Scope and Content Note
The Association for Union Democracy: Women's Project Records describe the activities and work of the Women's Project from its creation in 1985 into the early 2000s. These files include printed ephemera, newsletters and circulars, correspondence, serial publications, court cases, and organizational reports. The collection contains records created and collected by the Women's Project that correspond to its work and mission as an advocate for women in unions and nontraditional trades.
The collection is divided into the following three series: Series I: Association for Union Democracy, 1979-2002; Series II: The Women's Project, 1971-2002; and Series III: Subject and Organization Files, 1974-2002. The first series is comprised of records created by the Association for Union Democracy and kept by the Women's Project. These files include printed ephemera, newsletters and circulars, and organizational reports. The series also contains administrative documents, such as correspondence from the Association for Union Democracy as well as notes and agendas from the organization's Board of Directors meetings.
Series II contains meeting minutes, correspondence, circulars, printed ephemera, and resources created and collected by the Women's Project. These records describe activities conducted by the project, such as workshops and conferences, as well as events attended. The Project's "Intake," or complaints and questions, are notable as they describe the concerns and issues surrounding women and unions in the 1990s and early 2000s. The activities and published materials created by the Women's Project focus on issues of sexual discrimination and harassment at work and within trade unions.
Series III contains resources collected by the Women's Project on particular subjects and organizations related to the Project's mission. Most of the materials are printed ephemera and publications but they also include academic papers, newspaper clippings, public hearings, and court cases. Records from legal cases include important cases, such as Lois Robinson v. Jacksonville Shipyards and New York City hearings on discrimination in the construction industry. The project compiled materials from organizations all over the United States, but the majority of the records document organizations and government activities in the New York City metropolitan area. The series also includes printed materials on some minority groups, such as lesbian, African-American, and Latino-American tradeswomen.
NOTE: This collection is stored offsite, and advance notice is required for use.
Related Material at the Tamiment Library/Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Association for Union Democracy: Women's Project (OH 83)
Guide to the Printed Ephemera Collection on Organizations (PE 036)
Guide to the Printed Ephemera Collection on Trade Unions (PE 001)
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by Carl Biers (executive director), on behalf of the Association for Union Democracy, 2003. The accession number associated with this gift is 2003.025.
An additional gift was donated by Jane Latour at an unknown date. The accession number associated with this gift is 2018.058.
Sex discrimination against women -- United States.; Women labor union members |x Societies, etc.; Women labor leaders |z United States.; Labor unions; Women in the labor movement |z United States.; Women labor union members -- United States.; LaTour, Jane; Jennick, Susan; Association for Union Democracy; Biers, Carl; LaTour, Jane; Association for Union Democracy
- Series I: Association for Union Democracy, 1979-2002, 1979-2002 (Bulk 1990-2002); 306950; 0.75 Linear Feet
  Scope and Content Note
  The following series is comprised of records created by the Association for Union Democracy and kept by the Women's Project. These files include printed ephemera, newsletters and circulars, and organizational reports. The series also contains administrative documents, such as correspondence from Association for Union Democracy correspondence as well as notes and agendas from the organization's Board of Directors meetings.
  Arrangement
  Files are arranged alphabetically.
  - "$50/$75/$100 + Club News", 1991-2002; 306953 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Advertisements, 1991; 306954 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - "After the Teamsters Victory: The Next Steps for Union Democracy", 1992; 306955 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Annual Reports, 1987-1991; 306956 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Benson, Herman - Secretary Treasurer, Editor of Union Democracy Review, 1987-2001; 306957 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Biers, Carl - Executive Director, 2001; 306958 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Board of Directors Meetings, 1991-2002; 306959 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Circulars and Correspondence, 1989, 2000; 306960 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Court Cases In the Construction Trades, 1993-1999; 306961 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Democratic Rights of Union Members Workshop, 1997; 306962 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Fundraising Appeals, 2001; 306963 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Intake, 1989-1990; 306964 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Leaflets, undated; 306965 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Legal Rights of Union Membership, 1979-2001; 306966 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Letters of Support, 2001; 306967 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - "A New Stage in the Battle for Union Democracy": National Conference, 1990; 306968 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Report to the AUD Board of Directors, 2001-2002; 306969 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Spanish Language Literature, undated; 306970 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - T-Shirts - with AUD logo, undated; 306971 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - "Union Democracy in the Building Trades: A National Conference for Construction Union Activists", 2002; 306972 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - "Union Democracy in a Changing Labor Movement" Conference, 1999-2000; 306973 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - "Union Democracy in a Changing Labor Movement" Conference: "Pioneers and the Next Wave" Panel, 2000; 306974 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Union Democracy Review, 1986-2002; 306975 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Series II: The Women's Project, 1971-2002, 1971-2002 (Bulk 1985-2002); 306951; 5.25 Linear Feet
  Series II contains meeting minutes, correspondence, circulars, printed ephemera, and resources created and collected by the Women's Project of the Association for Union Democracy. These records describe activities conducted by the Women's Project, such as workshops and conferences, as well as events attended. The Project's "Intake," or complaints and questions, is of notable interest as they describe the concerns and issues surrounding women and unions in the 1990s and early 2000s. The activities and published materials created by the Women's Project focus on issues of sexual discrimination and harassment at work and within trade unions.
  - Advisory Board, 1988-1993; 306976 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Advisory Committee Meeting Minutes, 1991-2000; 306977 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Apprenticeship and Training in Trades, 1990-2001; 306978 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Association for Union Democracy National Conference, 1988; 306979 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Background and History (Includes Association for Union Democracy), 1987-1992; 306980 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Bishop, Brenda, undated; 306981 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Book Lists, 1999-2002; 306982 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Brochure (Activities, circa 1985-2000), c. 1985-2000; 306983 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Budgets (Includes Association for Union Democracy Budgets), 1971-2000; 306984 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Career and Apprenticeship Resources in New Jersey, c. 1991; 306985 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Circulars and Fliers, 1988-2000; 306986 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Class and Workshop Faxes and Correspondence, 1997-1998; 307573 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Conference Fliers (not Association for Union Democracy), 1983-2002; 307574 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Contract Negotiation and Ratification, c. 1986; 307575 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Contractors, 2001; 307576 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1986-2001; 307577 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Discrimination and the Law, 1990-2002; 307578 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Donations, 2001; 307579 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Duty of Fair Representation, c. 1980s; 307580 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Education/Teachers, 1988-1993; 307581 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Employment Discrimination Lawyers, 2001-2002; 307582 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Equitable Worksite Project, c. 1997; 307583 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Establishing a Women's Committee, c. 1991-1995; 307584 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Events Attended, c. 1998; 307585 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Events with the Association for Union Democracy, 2001; 307586 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Fact Sheets and Resource Lists, 1983-1989; 307587 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Final Reports, 1990; 307588 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - "Fundi: The Story of Ella Baker", Nov 2000; 307589 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Funding Plan, 1990-2002; 307590 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Grant Proposals, 1987-1991; 307591 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Grant Proposals, 1987-1999; 307592 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Grant Proposals, 1991-1997; 307593 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Grants Not Received, 2001; 307594 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Grants Received, 2000-2001; 307597 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Graphics, 1982-1991; 307595 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Handbook for Women In the Trades: Notes and Correspondence, 1990-1992; 307596 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Hiring Hall Handouts, 1990; 307598 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Intake, 1986-1989; 307599 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Intake, 2000-2001; 307600 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Internships, 1996-1998; 307601 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Jennik, Susan, 1987-1992; 307602 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Labor for Peace in the Persian Gulf, 1991; 307603 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Labor Songs, c. 1983; 307604 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Labor Video Fliers, 1989-1991; 307605 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - LaTour, Jane, 1989-2001; 307606 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - "Legal Rights for Union Women" Workshop, 1989-1991; 307607 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Letter to Women Workers, 1990; 307608 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Literature and Handout Originals, 1989-1990; 307609 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Mailing and Contact Lists, 1986-1991; 307610 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Mailing and Contact Lists, 1989-1994; 307611 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Mailings, 1985-1987; 307612 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - "Make Whole" Remedy, undated; 307613 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - "Manual for Survival: For Women in Nontraditional Employment", 1987-1991; 307614 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - "Manual for Survival: For Women in Nontraditional Employment" Revision, 2000; 307615 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Media and Publicity, 1989-1991; 307616 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Media and Publicity, 2001-2002; 307617 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - New York Advisory Committee, 2000-2001; 307618 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Non-Traditional Trades Recruitment, 2000-2002; 307619 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - "Nuts and Bolts of Organizing Women's Committees", May 2001; 307620 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Obituaries of Women's Rights Pioneers, 2000-2001; 307621 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Oral History Interviews, 2000; 307622 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Organizing Committee, 1987-1991; 307623 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - "Organizing Strategies for Union Women" Conference, Mar 1993; 307624 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Outreach, 1991-2000; 307625 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Pamphlets and Circulars, 1988, 2000; 307626 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Photographs and Negatives, undated; 307627 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Planning Committee Meetings: Agenda and Minutes, 1996; 307628 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Potential Allies, 2000; 307629 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Pre-Apprenticeship Training Resources, 1993; 307630 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Press List (I), 1997-2000; 307631 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Press List (II), 1997-2000; 307632 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Press; Publicity Guides, 1982-1988; 307633 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Publication Requests, 1985-1989; 307634 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - "Punch List", 2001-2002; 307635 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - "Punch List" Book Reviews, 2000-2001; 307636 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - "Punch List" Materials, 1999-2001; 307637 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - "Punch List" Organizations and Programs, 1999-2002; 307638 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - "Punch List" Public Relations, 2001; 307639 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - "Punch List" Subscriptions, 2001-2002; 307640 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Quality of Life / Standard of Living (I), 1985-1991; 307641 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Quality of Life / Standard of Living (II), 1985-1991; 307642 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Receipts and Expenses, 2000-2002; 307643 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Recruitment of Director, 1989; 307644 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Report to the Board, 2000; 307645 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Resources for Tradeswomen, 1994-2000; 307646 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Resources for Women, 1999-2000; 307647 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Ruderman, Evan, 2000; 307648 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Sexual Discrimination in Traditional vs. Non-Traditional Trades, 1996-2001; 307649 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Sexual Harassment Policy Draft, 1997-1998; 307650 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Sexual Harassment Policy, Materials Used for (I), 1981-1997; 307651 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Sexual Harassment Policy, Materials Used for (II), 1981-1997; 307652 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Sexual Harassment Policy, Orders for, 1997; 307653 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Sexual Harassment Resources, c. 1990-2000; 307654 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "Sexual Harassment at Work Know Your Rights", Sep 2000; 307655 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Speeches and Addresses, undated; 307656 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Stationary Graphics, c. 2001; 307657 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Stickers, undated; 307658 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Support Letters, 1987-1996; 307659 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Television and Film Resources, 1995-2002; 307660 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - To Do Lists, 1998-2001; 307661 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Tradeswomen Conferences: National and Local, 1996-1997; 307662 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Tradeswomen Organizations Ephemera, 1996-2000; 307663 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - T-Shirt - AUD logo, 2002; 307664 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - "Union Democracy Review": Women's Project Updates, 1990-1991; 307665 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Union Democracy Workshop Outlines, c. 1991; 307666 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Union Ephemera, 2000-2001; 307667 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Union Facts, 1991; 307668 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - "Union Women: Take the Lead!" Workshop, Oct 1990; 307669 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - "United Tradeswomen: Our Stories, Our Struggles", Oct 2000; 307670 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - "Using Union Democracy to Promote Women's Rights" Conference, Jun 1988; 307671 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - "Using Union Democracy to Promote Women's Rights" Conference, Jun 1988; 307674 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - "Using Union Power to Beat the Recession" Panel, May 1991; 307675 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - "Using Union Procedures to Promote Women's Issues" Workshop, 1989-2000; 307676 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Volunteers and Interns, 2001-2002; 307677 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Women of Color Organizations, 1999-2001; 307678 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Women in Unions, c. 1991; 307679 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - "Women in Unions" Conference, 1986; 307680 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - "Women in Unions: 'Organize, Don't Compromise'" Conference, Mar 1990; 307681 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - "Women in Unions: Rights and Realities" Conference, Dec 1988; 307682 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Women-Leaders in Unions, 1979-1993; 307683 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - "Women Take the Lead", 1998; 307684 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - "Women Take the Lead" Planning Committee Meeting January 31, 1997, 307685 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - "Women Take the Lead" Seminar Registration, 1998; 307686 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Women's Committees: Fact Sheets and Literature, 1978-2001; 307687 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Women's Groups, 1998-2000; 307688 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Women's Issues, 1980-1989; 307689 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Women's Stories Working in Non-Traditional Trades, 1998-2002; 307690 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - "A Workshop on Developing Leadership and Organizing Skills", 1990; 307691 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Workshops Spring of 1989, 307692 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Videos "Women of Steel", "United Tradeswomen", "Women in Operating Engineers", "Our History, Our Hopes. The IBEW in Michigan", "Local 40 Ironworkers", "FDNY Uniformed Women Firefighters" "Nontraditional Employment for Women", 2001, undated (Box Shared Tamiment 012, Cassette 9-15)
  - Minivideos: "Women Firefighters", undated (Box Shared Tamiment 012, Cassette 16-22)
- Series III: Subject and Organization Files, 1974-2004, 1947-2004 (Bulk 1980-2002); 306952; 14 Linear Feet
  The following series contains resources collected by the Women's Project on particular subjects and organizations related to the Project's mission. Most of the materials are printed ephemera and publications but also include academic papers, newspaper clippings, public hearings, and court cases. Records from legal cases include important cases, such as Lois Robinson v. Jacksonville Shipyards and New York City hearings on discrimination in the construction industry. The project compiled materials from organizations all over the United States, but the majority of the records document organizations and government activities in the New York City metropolitan area. The series also includes printed materials on some minority groups, such as lesbian, African-American, and Latino-American tradeswomen.
  - 9 to 5, National Association of Working Women, 1989-1993; 307747 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Aaron Diamond Foundation, 1989-1993; 307748 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Academic Papers, undated; 307749 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - "Access and Opportunity: Developing a Skilled Construction Labor Force in the Port Authority Region", 1989; 307750 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Adco Foundation, Inc., 1997-1998; 307751 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Affirmative Action, 1990-1991; 307752 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - African-American Workers, 1991; 307753 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Airport Employees' Union, 1992; 307754 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Alliance for Consumer Rights, 1998; 307755 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: "Labor Unity", 1990-1992; 307756 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU), 1989; 307757 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO), 1958, 1989-2001; 307758 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO): Racial and Gender Report Card, 1996-2002; 307759 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organization (AFL-CIO): Working Women's Department, 1996-2001; 307760 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 1984; 307761 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - American Labor Education Center: "American Labor", c. 1990; 307762 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Apprenticeship, 1977-1992; 307763 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - "Arbitration after Gilmer: Theory and Practice", undated; 307764 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Articles and Essays, 1986-1994; 307765 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Association of Legal Aid Attorneys: "Report on Salary Reopener Negotiations", 1992; 307766 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Astraea: The National Lesbian Action Foundation, 1992-2000; 307767 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Atran Foundation, Inc., 2000-2001; 307768 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Black Workers for Social Justice, 1989-1991; 307769 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Boehm Foundation, 2001; 307770 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Book Catalogs and Bibliographies, 1987-1991; 307771 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Boston Tradeswomen Network, 1983-2001; 307772 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Bread and Roses: "A Day in the Life of Working New York" Exhibition, 1990-2002; 307773 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Brecht Forum, 1998; 307774 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Building Trades: Discrimination, 1989-1990; 307775 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Bureau of National Affairs, Inc.: Union Labor Report, 2001; 307776 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Central Park East Secondary School, undated; 307777 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Chicago Actors Network, 1996-1997; 307778 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Chicago Women in Trades, 1990-2001; 307779 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Childcare and Pregnancy, 1980-1991; 307780 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Chinese Staff and Workers Association, 1988-1993; 307781 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Citizen Action of New York: Women's Rights at Work, 1998-2001; 307782 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - City of New York: Equal Employment Practices Commission, 2000-2001; 307783 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - City of New York: Office of the Comptroller Alan G. Hevesi, "Dilemma in the Millenium", Aug 1998; 307784 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Civil Rights Act of 1964, 1991; 307785 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Civil Rights Act of 1990, 1987-1990; 307786 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Civil Rights Act of 1991 and Pre-Existing Claims, 1991-1993; 307787 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Clerical Workers, 1984-1992; 307788 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Cleveland's Hard Hatted Women, 1989-1998; 307789 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Cleveland's Hard Hatted Women: Riveting News, 1986-1999; 307790 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Cleveland's Hard Hatted Women: Riveting News, 2000-2002; 307791 (Box 8, Folder 12)